icecat.us 2016-11-27

# Icecat Privacy Policy

Icecat Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting our website. Our privacy policy informs you how we use personal information collected on this site. The English version of the privacy form prevails over translations in case of any dispute. A translation is only made available for your convenience. Please, read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be amended, but any changes will be posted and changes will apply only to activities and information on a forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

 **Note:** the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this website only. If you link to other websites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.

Collection of Information

By registering to our catalogue or submitting a contact request or questions via our website we collect personal identifiable information such as names, postal addresses, email addresses, phone numbers etc., when voluntarily submitted by you, as a visitor or registered user. 

Disclosure of Personal Information

We may provide information about you to our employees in order to administer your account, and products and services provided to you by Icecat.We will not disclose your personal information without your permission to any third party unless we are required to do so by law. Should you breach our terms and conditions or terms of use or if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, we may disclose your information to a relevant authority. This may include exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction. Any disclosure of personal information will be strictly controlled and made fully in accordance with current Dutch law. Be sure that your information is used only to fulfil your specific request unless you give us permission to use it in another manner; for example, to add you to our mailing list (opt-in) or to provide your information to a business partner you want to connect to.

Use of performance data

Icecat will save performance data, including user statistics and user preferences, and other similar data (“Performance Data”) every time you download a data-sheet or register to our catalogue. Icecat may share anonymous Performance Data with specific partners, and other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation.

IP registration

Your IP address may also be recorded by us to protect and control content, as well as to create and evaluate performance data.

Cookies

We use cookies only to remember user preferences during a browser session on Icecat’s websites such as - but not limited to - language and country settings. Personal information is not collected via cookies. 

Commitment to Data Security

Your personal identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings, unless they are intrinsic to a service your subscribed to.

Privacy Contact Information

If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you can send them via the contact form.

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.
